lgeccu.org 2009-06-19

# LGE Community Credit Union

| 

LGE Community Credit Union, your member owned financial institution, is committed to providing you with competitive products and services to meet your financial needs and help you reach your goals. We are equally committed to protecting the privacy of our members. Under federal law, we are required to give you this privacy notice. It describes our Credit Union’s privacy policy and practices concerning the personal information we collect and disclose about our members. It also includes information about the parties who receive personal and sometimes nonpublic information from us as we conduct the business of the credit union.

If after reading this notice you have questions, please contact us at 770-421-2631 or 800-541-8921 x631  
Or write to: PRIVACY NOTICE  
                    LGE Community Credit Union  
                    430 Commerce Park Dr  
                    Marietta, GA 30060

_**Information we collect about you:**_ We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: (1) Information we receive from you on applications and other forms; (2) Information about your transactions with us; (3) Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency; (4) Information obtained when verifying the information you provide on an application or other forms; this may be obtained from your current or past employers, or from other institutions where you conduct financial transactions. We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, as permitted by law.

_**Parties who receive information from us:**_ We may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to the following types of third parties.

|   | • | **Financial service providers** , such as insurance companies, mortgage service companies, and securities broker-dealers  
---|---|---  
  | • | **Non-financial companies** , such as consumer reporting agencies, data processors, check/share draft printers, financial statement publishers, plastic card processors, direct marketers, and government agencies  
  
**Disclosure of information to parties that provide services to us** : In order for us to conduct the business of the Credit Union, we may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing or other services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements so that we may provide members competitive products and services. We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you under circumstances as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to process transactions on your behalf, conduct the operations of our credit union, follow your instructions as you authorize, or protect the security of our financial records.

To protect our members’ privacy, we only work with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of information we provide. We do not permit these companies to sell the information we provide to other third parties.

_**How to opt out or stop certain disclosures about you:**_ If you prefer that we do not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures – you may direct us not to make those disclosures (other than disclosures permitted by law). If you wish to opt out of the disclosures to nonaffiliated third parties, you may select one of the following:

  | • | Call the following number: (770-421-2631 or 800-541-8921 x631)  
---|---|---  
  | • | Write to us at the following address and include your name, all account numbers which you sign on that you wish to be included, date and a signature:  
  |   |                     PRIVACY POLICY   
                    LGE Community Credit Union  
                    430 Commerce Park Dr  
                    Marietta, GA 30060  
  
You may opt out of these disclosures at any time. This opt out, by law, will not apply to disclosures that are legally permitted or disclosure we make to companies that perform services on our behalf or to other financial institutions that have joint marketing agreements with us.

Once we receive your request, we have a reasonable amount of time to stop the disclosures. You may always contact us for assistance if you wish to later revoke your opt out election.

_**How we protect your information:**_ We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and/or procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.
